From the 2024.1 version, we have improved the measurement point function, which can be achieved in the measurement in the version.
Through this video, let's learn in detail how to use the measurement point tool.
Now, when you choose the measurement point tool, you will automatically enter the function mode of measuring the length of the line.
You can see that the point of the mouse at this time will be the same deep red as the inner line.
We can use it to measure the straight line distance on the board, the curve distance, and the multi-line distance.
The text next to the light bar prompts you.
When you press the P key, it will switch to the length of the measurement board.
Press the P key to switch modes.
At this time, you can see that the mouse's dot is blue and the prompt changes.
When you press the P key, it will switch to the length of the measurement straight line and the length of the line.
The translation of the current version has not been updated.
It will be corrected later.
Press the P key again to switch back.
Let's first learn the length of the line measurement mode.
The way to use this tool is to press the start button.
In the measurement process, you can press the multi-line measurement again.
Double click to end.
You can also press the control key to create a curve.
The operation of this operation is completely the same as the operation of the internal line.
The latest version allows you to start and end the measurement at any position in the board.
Then we can also use the edit measurement point tool.
Let's move and edit the measurement point.
If you don't need it, we can delete it.
First, let's measure the length of the front piece.
That is, the front palm of the costume.
Press the shift key to control the vertical direction.
Double click to end.
You can see that a new measurement point will appear in the window on the right side of the object.
And because this board has code information,
all the size of the horse can be obtained at once.
Then we can modify its name.
You can also use this mode.
Measure the distance from the top to the end of the board.
For example, measure the width of the front.
If you find that the measured line is a virtual line and the display size of the object window is 0.
Then we need to switch to the edit measurement point tool.
Select this measurement line.
Right-click to display the length.
Finally, use it to measure the chest.
It can be used to measure the width of the board.
Press the start button.
Press the middle button.
Press the shift key to control the horizontal direction.
Double click to end.
You can also use this mode.
We have to move to the correct position.
Press the left button to change the direction of the board.
If you see that the position is exactly the same as the position of your foot,
press the start button to change the direction.
And we can input a specific value to achieve a positioning in the picture.
Press the start button.
Press the right button while moving.
Then click the specifically input data window.
Click OK
Then we will switch the texture surface
The top of the left of our post
To our previous point
Then switch back to the black and white surface
Next, we press the P key to switch to the length measurement of the outside of the board
The way to use this tool is in any position of the outside of the board
The operation of single-click start, single-click end and free sewing tool is the same
Then we can measure the length of the T-stitch embroidery mountain curve
We turn back toанию
pouco of information on the positions just measured
Make another course
In addition to this tool
Also to find the manufactured tools
In addition to measuring the curve, we can also use the hook and loop tool to measure the curve.
Select the pre-sew dragon curve and right-click to hook it as a measuring point.
You can also measure the distance of this curve.
Now we switch to the edit measurement tool and select the pre-sew dragon right-click that we just measured.
We can see the selection of the menu.
Select the length of the straight line.
The current line is the value length of the T-shape.
So, we can make a switch between the two measurements.
And,
We can also see the length of the X-shape and the length of the Y-shape.
And make a reverse of it.
Finally, switch back to the length of the straight line.
And,
We can see that all the measured values are displayed in a corresponding line in the 3D clothing.
If we need to hide it, we can hide it in the clothing information display.
We can hide it in the 2D size display.
If we want to hide it, we can hide it in the 3D size display.
In the object window, it will also correspond to a length of a 3D line.
Select this option.
You can check the length of the 3D line in the object window.
And in the property editor, you can check the length difference between the 2D and 3D lines.
What is the difference?
It is because the clothing version has been simulated.
Due to a stretch in the gravity of the fabric.
And some effects of the artificial structure and the model wearing it.
There will be a certain degree of deformation.
Finally, let's take a look at the storage and use of measurement data.
After editing the measurement data that needs to be stored.
Use the storage button in the upper right corner of the object window.
The measurement data is stored into a CSV file.
This file is a table format file.
Use the office software to open and check it.
When we need to measure some new styles.
You can also directly open this style.
At this time, we can cut to.
The measurement point of the object window.
Open the CSV file just saved.
You can see that in the object window column.
There is already a place to measure.
No need to fill in every time.
Switch to the measurement tool.
Select the position we need to measure.
Press in the position of the length.
Make sure there is a contrast in front.
Prove that we have chosen the corresponding position.
Then we measure.
Press start.
Double click to finish.
Then we can measure the position.
It can be filled directly into the blue.
If we need to measure some new positions.
You can also directly click to add.
Fill in the position we need to measure first.
Then measure.
Finally, let's take a look.
There is such an application button at the back.
Then we can choose our data.
Then click on the application.
It can be filled into the required column.
The above is the introduction of all measurement tool.
I hope you can use this function better in the course.